{
    "id": "1998418605a54a3babd32b7c6aae5299",
    "title": "Present tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9d188560ae0e48a5b1c346786ee382f0",
            "title": "Present Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Water …………………………… at 100 degree Celsius.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "boil",
                        "boils",
                        "is boiling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………… tennis every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "play",
                        "plays",
                        "am playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The earth ……………………………. around the sun.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "move",
                        "moves",
                        "is moving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "James …………………………………. for an insurance company.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "works",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In Act I, Hamlet ……………………………….. the ghost of his father.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "meet",
                        "meets",
                        "has met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The kettle ……………………………….. Shall I make tea?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "boil",
                        "boils",
                        "is boiling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………………. this song very much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "likes",
                        "am liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………………. to the theater this evening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "are going",
                        "have gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His train ……………………………… at",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrive",
                        "arrives",
                        "is arriving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will phone you when I …………………………….. home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "gets",
                        "am getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}